<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
    xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog
        http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-4.20.xsd">

    <changeSet id="039-populate-brand-a-legal-pages" author="platform">
        <sql>
            UPDATE site_settings SET legal_pages = '{"privacy":"&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Prism Migration, accessible from &lt;a href=\"https://prismmigration.com\"&gt;https://prismmigration.com&lt;/a&gt;, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Prism Migration and how we use it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Information We Collect&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We collect information directly from you when you register, buy software licenses, or contact our support team. This may include your name, email address, transaction history, and machine-identifying IP details to authenticate and manage your product license keys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. How We Use Your Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We use the collected data to verify active product licensing, prevent fraudulent license redistribution, distribute software updates, and deliver responsive support services at support@prismmigration.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. Data Protection &amp; Security&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;All payment operations are handled securely by PCI-DSS compliant third-party payment gateways. We do not store credit card details. License checking is executed locally on client machines using secure 256-bit SSL connections.&lt;/p&gt;","terms":"&lt;h2&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Prism Migration. By accessing &lt;a href=\"https://prismmigration.com\"&gt;https://prismmigration.com&lt;/a&gt; or downloading our software products, you agree to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. License to Use&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We grant you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, and revocable license to use our data tools in accordance with the purchased tier specifications (Standard, Business, or Enterprise).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Restrictions&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are explicitly prohibited from reverse engineering, redistributing, leasing, or sharing single-machine activation keys with unauthorized third parties. Violations will result in immediate license termination without a refund.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. Limitation of Liability&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In no event shall Prism Migration be held liable for any data loss, system downtime, or commercial damages arising from the use or inability to use our software products.&lt;/p&gt;","refund":"&lt;h2&gt;Refund Policy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We value customer satisfaction and stand behind our products. We offer a &lt;strong&gt;30-day money-back guarantee&lt;/strong&gt; on all software purchases to ensure our customers find the software suitable for their needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Guarantee Conditions&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If our software is unable to perform as advertised, and our support team cannot resolve the technical problem, you are eligible to request a full refund within 30 days of the purchase transaction date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. How to Request a Refund&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send an email to support@prismmigration.com including your original order receipt, transaction ID, license key details, and a brief description of the technical issue you encountered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. License Deactivation&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upon approval and processing of the refund, all associated product license keys and active machine activations will be immediately deactivated and blacklisted from our licensing validation server.&lt;/p&gt;","license":"&lt;h2&gt;License Agreement (EULA)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This End User License Agreement (EULA) is a binding legal agreement between you (an individual or entity) and Prism Migration for the software product accompanying this agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. License Grant&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prism Migration grants you a personal, non-transferable, non-exclusive license to install and run the software on the number of devices specified in your purchase order (e.g., 1 computer for Standard, up to 25 for Enterprise).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Intellectual Property Rights&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The software, its code, structure, design, and assets are the exclusive intellectual property of Prism Migration and are protected by international copyright laws. No title or property rights are transferred to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. Termination&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This agreement terminates automatically if you fail to comply with any of its terms. Upon termination, you must cease all use of the software and permanently uninstall it from all devices.&lt;/p&gt;"}' WHERE site_id = 'brandA';
        </sql>
    </changeSet>
</databaseChangeLog>
